So I was able to dig up from 2005. He
would have been 14 or 15 years old.
>> Not bad.
>> This has to be around the time throw
made in my mind. But that chord for
sure, seventh chord on a synth is so
Tyler literally never goes away in his
entire career. So I did find one of his
earliest albums. It's a EP called
Stereotype. Like I eat shoes. I rock ice
cream sneaks. Cause it looking like a
wall fashion week.
I'm a supreme freak. Fox [__] babes on
my feet.
>> So I don't know if it was like his
producer name or what, but he also had a
alias called polymano. Have you heard of
this at all?
>> No.
>> Paulie/mono I think was either another
character or alias or it was his
producer name because he released this
project called Pink Gold Square Pixels.
Okay, I'm [__] with this. That's
>> You can start to get the darker.
>> You can hear some like Odd Future ramped
up vocals to this.
>> Yes.